

Deok-Kyeong (DK), JANG Seoul/Korea +82 10 2898 1777 dk.jang1014@gmail.com

personal page in linkedin og github

ABOUT

I'm a Co-founder/CTO at movin and also a Postdoc in Motion Computing Lab at KAIST. Before that, I interned at Meta Reality Labs. My research goal is to improve the quality of digital character motion in computer graphics and AR/VR systems using deep learning methods. I currently focus on the real-time motion characterization and 3D full-body motion capture using a single LiDAR.

EDUCATION _

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

2017-2022 / South Korea

Ph.D. in Computer Graphics / Motion Computing Laboratory / Advisor: Sung-Hee Lee

• Research on virtual motion stylization/characterization, motion synthesis/control and manifold space.

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

2015-2017 / South Korea

M.S. in Computer Graphics / Motion Computing Laboratory / Advisor: Sung-Hee Lee

• Research on regression-based landmark detection of Human Models.

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

2009-2015 / South Korea

B.S. in Physics and Mathematics

• Research on modeling the prey-predator system.

PUBLICATION

Motion Puzzle: Arbitrary Motion Style Transfer by Body Part

2022

ACM Transactions on Graphics (TOG) / ACM SIGGRAPH 2022

Deok-Kyeong Jang, Soomin Park and Sung-Hee Lee

Diverse Motion Stylization for Multiple Style Domains via Spatial-Temporal Graph-Based Generative Model

2021

Proceedings of the ACM on Computer Graphics and Interactive Techniques (PACMCGIT) / SCA Soomin Park, Deok-Kyeong Jang, and Sung-Hee Lee

Constructing Human Motion Manifold With Sequential Networks

2020

Computer Grahpics Forum (CGF) / Eurographics 2021

Deok-Kyeong Jang and Sung-Hee Lee

Regression-Based Landmark Detection on Dynamic Human Models

2017

Computer Grahpics Forum (CGF) / Pacific graphics

Deok-Kyeong Jang and Sung-Hee Lee

WORK EXPERIENCE _

CTO / Co-founder

2023.03 - now / movin

Product: 3D full-body motion capture solution using a single LiDAR.

• Developed real-time full-body motion capture framework based on a single LiDAR, incorporating global translation tracking.Constructing a high-quality dataset featuring diverse subjects, containing synchronized LiDAR point cloud and optical motion capture data for a wide range of actions.

Research Science Intern

2022.05 - 2022.10 / Meta Reality Lab, Redmond, USA

Manager: Yuting Ye, Research Scientist in Gemini team

Collaborators: Dr.Jungdam Won, Research Scientist from Meta AI

• Research on motion characterization in real-time, enhancement of motion style transfer and retargeting with various input sensors.

PROJECTS

Motion tracking and characterization research for virtual avatars

2022 - 2023

Meta Platforms Technologies

• As a researcher of the project, developed real-time motion characterization framework for virtual avatars.

Study of styled motion generation for non-verbal communication of virtual human agents

2020 - 2022

National Research Foundation of Korea

• As a leading researcher of the project, developed humanoid agent's appearance-style customizable motion generation framework.

Development of 4D Reconstruction and Dynamic Deformable Action Model based Hyper Realistic Service Technology

2017 - 2021

Ministry of Science, ICT and Future Planning, Giga Korea Project

• As a leading researcher of the project, developed motion style transfer method and plugins to automatically generate stylized motion.

Development of Simulation Software for Human Body-Sport Gear Complex

2015 - 2017

for Rapidly Prototyping Customized Sports Gear

Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism

• As a main developer of the project, developed an sports gear modeling technique that fits the personalized foot shape and sports gear interaction.

PAPER REVIEWER _

SIGGRAPH, SIGGRAPH ASIA, Pacific Graphics, Computer Graphics Forum, IEEE Transactions on Visualization and Computer Graphics (TVCG)

TECHNICAL SKILLS __

Programming Languages Python | C# | C/C++ | Matlab

Operating Systems Mac OS X | Linux/Unix | Windows

Frameworks & Libraries PyTorch | Tensorflow | Eigen | igl | Numpy | etc.

Tools Unity | Blender | Docker System | etc.